Guide to the National Council on Religion and Public Education Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Other Organizations, Series X; Series X, Other Organizations, is an alphabetical listing of many organizations in the field of religion and public education. The most extensive file is of the Public Education Religion Studies Center at Wright State University, which was funded by the Religious Heritage of America Foundation and the Lilly Endowment, and had as leaders James Panoch, David Barr, Jim Uphoff and Nick Piediscalzi.
  - American Academy of Religion (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - American Association of School Administrators (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - American Council on Education (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - American Jewish Committee (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Americans for Religious Liberty (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Americans United Research Foundation (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Baptist Joint Committee on Public Affairs (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Bicentennial Conference on Religious Liberty (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - California State Board of Education (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Catholic Bishops (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Christian Conference of Connecticut (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Citizens for Equal Access (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Placement of Religion, North Carolina (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Connecticut Conference, United Church of Christ (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Council for Religion in Independent Schools (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Drake University (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Episcopal Church (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Gallup Poll (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Harvard Educational Review (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Iowa Project (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Iowa State University (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Laymen's National Bible Committee (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Mary Ann Spangler (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Minnesota Council of Churches (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous organizations (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - National Association of Episcopal Schools (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - National Catholic Educational Association (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - National Coalition Against Censorship (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - National Council of Churches (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - National School Public Relations Association (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - National Council of Social Studies (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - New York City Released Time (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Religious Dimensions of American History (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Religious Heritage of America (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Religious Instruction Association (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Synagogue Council of America (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - United Church Board for Homeland Ministries (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - United Methodist Church (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Public Education Religion Studies Center, 1972-1976 (Box 26, Folder 41-46)
  - PERSC Advisory Council (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - PERSC Book manuscripts (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - PERSC Newsletters, 1973-79 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - PERSC Resources (Box 26, Folder 50-51)
  - PERSC Packet (Box 26, Folder 52)